g-wonlinetextbooks.com 2017-07-20

# Privacy Policy

This website is provided by Goodheart-Willcox Publisher. By using this website, you consent to the use of your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy.

Collection and Use of Personal Data  
Your privacy is important to Goodheart-Willcox Publisher. We at times collect, retain, and utilize Personal Data about you to operate our business, including collecting feedback from you, notifying you about new titles and opportunities to access content of interest to you. The term “Personal Data” means personally identifiable information that Goodheart-Willcox Publisher obtains about you, including your name, email address, and feedback you provide. We do not collect Personal Data about you through the website unless you voluntarily provide it.  If you voluntarily provide your email address or other contact information, we may use it to inform you of new titles or other updates to our products.

Log Files  
Some information is gathered on the website automatically and stored in log files and other data formats. This information, which does not identify you, includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.  This information may be used to track user habits and improve the functionality of the website.  Cookies are used to track this information anonymously. Cookies are small data files that a website can place on a user’s computer to allow the website to store and retrieve data about that particular user so that the website can perform a variety of tasks and functions. The information stored in these cookies is not linked to any of your Personal Data.

Disclosure of Information  
Except as indicated within this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, rent, or otherwise share or transfer your Personal Data with third parties. We may transfer Personal Data to third-party vendors who act for us for further processing in accordance with the purposes for which the data was originally collected or for purposes to which you have subsequently consented. All Goodheart-Willcox Publisher vendors operate under federal and state laws regarding consumer privacy.

Personal Data may be disclosed where permitted or required by law, to comply with legal process, to protect the security or integrity of our databases or the website, to protect our business or reputation, to take precautions against legal liability, to protect and defend our rights or property, for required institutional risk control, or for resolving disputes, inquiries or complaints with respect to your use of the website.

Changes in Goodheart-Willcox Publisher Privacy Statements  
Goodheart-Willcox Publisher may at any time revise the privacy policy by updating this posting.
